Guide to the Jonathan Edwards College, Yale University, Ephemera
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Jonathan Edwards College, Yale University, ephemera
1997-2001
RU 894
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
(2 boxes)
The material consists of exhibition catalogs, programs, a DVD, and invitations to events and exhibitions at Jonathan Edwards College, Yale University.
Jonathan Edwards College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-H-2 (YRG 13-H-2), Records of the master of Jonathan Edwards College.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The material consists of exhibition catalogs, programs, a DVD, and invitations to events and exhibitions at Jonathan Edwards College, Yale University.
Art -- Exhibitions; College students; Student housing; Jonathan Edwards College (Yale University); Yale University -- Student housing; Yale University -- Students
- Printed material documenting events and exhibitions at Jonathan Edwards College, Yale University, 1997-2001; Series I
  - Exhibitions
    - 1997 (Box 1)
    - 1998 (Box 1)
    - 1999 (Box 1)
    - 2000 (Box 1)
    - 2001 (Box 1)
    - 2002 (Box 1)
  - Master's Tea
    - 1999 (Box 1)
    - 2001 (Box 1)
  - Performance, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Plays, 2000 (Box 1)
- "Four Saints in Three Acts" [videorecording], 2003; Accession 2005-A-134
  - "Four Saints in Three Acts: An Opera," by Gertrude Stein and Virgil Thomson, performed by Yale Undergraduates with cameo faculty appearances, in conjunction with the Department of Music and School of Drama, sponsored by the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscripts Library. computer files (DVD-Video), 2003
    General note
    Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 1U)